Victoria Martynenko

3D Artist

Contacts

+447578100561 i.v.v@live.com

Links

Portfolio Behance LinkedIn

Skills

Autodesk 3ds Max

Adobe Photoshop

Corona Render

Vray

Marvelous Designer

Forest Pack

Substance Painter

ZBrush

Languages

English

Ukrainian

Russian

Hobbies

I like drawing, listening to music, and reading new scientific research on various topics.

Profile

I am a visualiser who focuses on high quality and photorealistic work.

Always improving my skills to create an interesting, realistic and salable image.

I have a responsible approach, perseverance, attention to details because

I love my job.

I have experience in freelance and in the office in a team.

Employment History

3D visualisation/modeling, Freelance

2016 - 2021

I have worked with an architect, for architectural design companies and for furniture manufacturing companies.

Responsibilities:

- Interior visualisation of private apartments and office premises according to the terms of reference from the architect;
- Interior visualisation based on references or wishes of the clients;
- Furniture modeling;
- Create textures from photos;
- Exterior visualisation;
- Final rendering with post-processing in Photoshop.

3D Artist, Digital Partners Global

MARCH 2021 - JULY 2021

Responsibilities:

- Interior visualisation for VR tour applications;
- Creation of low-poly interior models for VR tours;
- Modeling low-poly houses for masterplans;
- Creation of streets and parks for masterplans;
- Modeling of objects and locations with UV unwrapping;
- Floorplans.

Education

Software Engineer, Department of Technical cybernetics, Dnipropetrovsk National University of Railway Transport V. Lazaryan, Dnipro, Ukraine 2008 - 2013

2008 - 2013

Courses

Computer graphics and design (2D Graphics and Layout using Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign; Create static web pages using HTML and CSS, UI/UX basics; 3D Graphics), Branch of the Computer Academy "STEP", Dnipro, Ukraine 2011 - 2013